TAYLOR ALTMAN

Website moderated: http://melio.tv/ Website Moderated: www.casamona.com

Professional Summary

Being a recent graduate student I am a highly motivated individual who has sought to test his skills in a variety of industries, ranging from services to media and marketing. I have spent the past 2 years since graduation expanding my programming skills and web knowledge working at several companies within Europe; focusing on their web products. Most recently I have been enrolled in Programming Boot camp based in Barcelona where I have improved my Ruby, Javascript, HTML and CSS skills.

Skillsanguages (Native in English and proficient in

Spanish) Have worked extensively with Photo shop

Avid Certified Pro tools certified

CSS and HTML5 Previous experience on a marketing team

Ruby and Javascript Adobe Illustrator experience

Have lead several social media Campaigns

Experience in Customer Service

Extensive Knowledge of Atlassian

Work History
Customer Service Agent

01/2016 to 08/2016

Castlabs—Berlin
I have recently moved back from Berlin where I was an integral part of a customer service team for a DRM and web

services company. I mainly aided in customer relations and made sure the developers were being signed the correct tickets from our CRM systems. It was through this job I realized I needed to improve my development skills so I could improve my understanding of technical problems.

Head videographer 09/2014 to 04/2015

ATG – Oxford Over the last year of my university I have started a job doing photography and videography for the majority of night clubs around Oxford. Not only has this allowed me to practice my production skills using Avid and Premiere, but it also allowed me to develop an understanding of how a professional media company operates and the requirements expected of a professional level product.

Reference: ATG Media: Head videographer, Jonathan <u>Dunbar-JrDunbar100@gmail.com</u> <u>Intern-Marketing and Design</u> 06/2013 to 08/2015

Melio - Barcelona

Over the past two summer I have worked at a live streaming and app development company with ties to companies such as MTV and Canal + called Melio. While I was there I spent my time either aiding in market research or moderating and helping in the design of the website.

Reference: Melio: Intern, Giuseppe Flores D'aircas – <u>gflores@melio.tv</u> Marketing team- Web Moderating

08/2015 to Current

Casamona – Barcelona after graduating from university I have been working for a real estate agency in Barcelona called Casamona where I was working with the marketing team whilst moderating their website. Working for Casamona helped me understand the world of online marketing in new depth; I have had to build my understanding of SEO and CRM systems to the point where I had to be able to explain in depth to people of lesser understanding about these topics, which challenged my capabilities as a web developer in ways that it hasn't been before. Reference: Casamona: Marketing/IT, Tine Mathiassen Tine@casamona.com Reference: Academic: Jon Dempsey - j.dempsey@brookes.ac.uk

Education
Bachelor of Science: Media Technology

Oxford Brookes University - Oxford

Received a high 2:1 Degree

3.4 GPA

Sound Design and Audio Programming coursework

Public Relations and Media Relations coursework
For my dissertation I researched, planned and executed experiments comparing and contrasting different several video codecs and their places in the market; specifically Google's stance on a royalty free alternative to the industry dominating H.264 And their next generation of HD and UHD compression systems.

High School Diploma:

Benjamin Franklin School - Barcelona

2012

2015

High School Diploma:

Bard Early College - New york

High School Diploma:

United World College - Singapore

2004